Name: Julián Andrés Misnaza Morales e-mail: <u>julianmisnaza@gmail.com</u>

phone: +573505070449

#### **Career Summary**

Julian Misnaza works as a backend Software Engineer, skilled in technologies such as Java, Spring, Python, TypeScript, AWS, Big Data (Learning), GCP, relational databases, and non-relational databases like MongoDB and dynamodb.

Experience in analysis, design, and development of cross-platform applications within the framework of agile work methodologies such as Scrum.

# **Summary of Qualifications**

## Proficient In:

- JavaJEE
- WebServices
- Tomcat
- IBM WASWeblogic
- PL/SQL
- Spring

- Hibernate
- Maven
- PythonHTML, XML,
- JavaScript
- Git
- Jira
- Postman

- TDD
- Agile
- ScrumSQL
- SQL
- DockerKubernetes
- Scala

- Hadoop
- Spark
- Microservices
- DDD
- TypeScript

# Languages

• Spanish (native speaker)

English (professional working proficiency)

# **Career History**

### Novacomp - Novashore

Dec 2021 - Nov 2022

# Sr Software Developer

As a Software developer, I have worked on two different accounts. The main purpose in both cases is to develop and maintain the microservices involved in the last developments. This includes having a meeting with a business person and giving priority to the sprint to document, develop and test this new feature or bug fix.

#### Using:

- Java 8, SpringBoot, Kubernetes, Azure, JUnit, TestNG, GitHub, Confluence, Scrum
- TypeScript, NestJS, GitHub, Jira, Confluence, Scrum, AWS

#### **Freelance Developer**

July 2021 – Dec 2021

#### Software Developer

Feature development and support for financial entities.

As a software developer, I understand the client's requirements and translate them into code. The main tools I have used are Jira to keep track of stories, Git as a repository, and development is mainly in Java on the microservices architecture.

# Using:

Java, JUnit, Spring Batch, Spring Boot, Spring Data, MicroServices, AWS, GitHub, Confluence

**Globant** Feb 2020 – Jun 2021

Java Developer Sr

Feature development and testing for the FIS project.

Using:

Java, GraphQL, Dagger, AWS, GIT, Jenkins, Terraform, Cucumber

Feature development and migration for the CBS project.

Using:

Java, GCP, GIT, IDL.

• Feature development and migration for the MissionLane project.

Using:

Python, GCP, Terraform, Kubernetes, Docker, AWS

# Lean Factory, Bogotá, Colombia

Jun 2018 - Aug 2019

Senior Software Developer

- Design, development, and testing of the solutions proposed in joint work with the chamber of commerce team.
- Build architecture documentation.
- Deliver and go along with artifacts deploy

# Farmatodo®, Bogotá, Colombia

Dec 2016 - May. 2018

Software Developer

- Design and develop rest web services to build the deliveries app on multi-channel to Farmatodo.
- Code improvement.
- Production support.
- To build ETL in SSIS tool to migrate information from core business

# Certicámara, Bogotá, Colombia

Sep. 2015 – Oct 2016

Senior Software Developer

- As a team lead my role was to lead the "certifactura" migration to be accepted by the DIAN as a certified billing and develop a system to manage invoices and payments.
- Meet with the client and provider to define requirements.
- Design and develop components

#### STAR INTELIGENCIA Y TECNOLOGÍA

Jan 2012 – Jun

2014

Senior Software Developer

- As a team lead my primary role was to lead the development of the BA tools HORUS and HEIMDAL.
- I defined technical requirements
- Analysis, documentation and develop
- To have meetings with clients to define requirements

#### **Education**

# **Andes University: Master of Information Engineering.**, Bogota

Jan 2019 -

Master of Engineering – MEng

## **Distrital University: Telematic Engineering.**, Bogota

Jan 2013 - Aug 2017

BS, Telematic Engineering